export const quizData = [
    {
        id:1,
        question:"1.What is the name of the Curse occupying Yuji Itadori's body in 'Jujutsu Kaisen'?",
        option:{
            a:'Jogo',
            b:'Gojo Saturu',
            c:'Mahito',
            d:'Ryomen Sukuna',
            
        },
        answer:{d:'Ryomen Sukuna'}     
    },
    {
        id:2,
        question:'2.What two colors are used in the Amestris flag in "Fullmetal Alchemist"?',
        option:{
            a:'Green and Yellow',
            b:'Green and Black',
            c:'Black and White',
            d:'Green and White',
        },    
        answer:{c:'Green and White'}    
    },
    {
        id:3,
        question:"3.Who is Isabella's child by blood in 'The Promised Neverland''?",
        option:{
            a:'Emma',
            b:'Sarah',
            c:'Peter',
            d:'Ray',
        },       
        answer:{d:'Ray'}
    },
    {
        id:4,
        question:"4.What is All Might's Quirk called in 'My Hero Academia'?",
        option:{
            a:'One For All',
            b:'Sugar Rush',
            c:'Tail',
            d:'Pop Off',
        },     
        answer:{a:'One For All'}  
    },
    {
        id:5,
        question:"5.What powers and abilities does Envy possess in 'Fullmetal Alchemist'?",
        option:{
            a:'Immortality',
            b:'Shapeshifting',
            c:'Regeneration',
            d:'All Of Them',
        },        
        answer:{d:'All Of Them'}
    },
    {
        id:6,
        question:"6.Which person in 'Naruto' is a kunoichi?",
        option:{
            a:'Sakura',
            b:'Kiba',
            c:'Naruto',
            d:'Shino',
        },
        answer:{a:'Sakura'}
    },
    {
        id:7,
        question:'7.What is the one beverage that ghouls can consume without getting sick in "Tokyo Ghoul"?',
        option:{
            a:'Orange Juice',
            b:'Grape Soda',
            c:'Coffee',
            d:'Alcohol',
        },       
        answer:{c:'Coffee'}
    },
    {
        id:8,
        question:'8.Who is the main protagonist in "Demon Slayer: Kimetsu no Yaiba"?',
        option:{
            a:'Gon Freecss',
            b:'Tanjiro Kamado',
            c:'Nezuko Kamado',
            d:'Hisoka',
        },        
        answer:{b:'Tanjiro Kamado'}
    },
    {
        id:9,
        question:'9.Which village are Asta and Yuno from in "Black Clover"?',
        option:{
            a:'Alubarna',
            b:'Castle Town',
            c:'Hage',
            d:'Ecbatana',
        },        
        answer:{c:'Hage'}
    },
    {
        id:10,
        question:'10.Which anime tells the story of Saitama, a superhero who can defeat any opponent with a single hit?',
        option:{
            a:'Dragon Ball Z',
            b:'Black Clover',
            c:'Naruto',
            d:'One-Punch Man',
        },        
        answer:{d:'One-Punch Man'}
    },
    {
        id:11,
        question:'11.Lord Boros is the leader of what group in "One-Punch Man"?',
        option:{
            a:'The Pirates',
            b:'Saitama Group',
            c:'Dark Matter Thieves',
            d:'Alienation',
        },        
        answer:{c:'Dark Matter Thieves'}
    },
    {
        id:12,
        question:'12.Who deceived Naruto into stealing a sacred scroll?',
        option:{
            a:'Hashirama',
            b:'Kakashi',
            c:'Akatsuki',
            d:'Mizuki',
        },        
        answer:{d:'Mizuki'}
    },
    {
        id:13,
        question:'13.Where is the scar located on Scars body in "Fullmetal Alchemist"?',
        option:{
            a:'His Back',
            b:'His Chest',
            c:'His Face',
            d:'His Foot',
        },        
        answer:{c:'His Face'}
    },
    {
        id:14,
        question:`14.What is Endeavor's Quirk called in "My Hero Academia"?`,
        option:{
            a:'Flame Thrower',
            b:'Hellflame',
            c:'Fire',
            d:'Hellfire',
        },        
        answer:{b:'Hellflame'}
    },
    {
        id:15,
        question:'15.Which one is a wall on Paradise Island that protected the remnants of Eldia in "Attack on Titan"?',
        option:{
            a:'Maria',
            b:'All of Them',
            c:'Sina',
            d:'Rose',
        },
        answer:{b:'All of Them'}
    },
    {
        id:16,
        question:'16.Who does Yuji Itadori live with at the beginning of "Jujutsu Kaisen"?',
        option:{
            a:'His Grandmother',
            b:'His Father',
            c:'His Grandfather',
            d:'His Mother',
        },        
        answer:{c:'His Grandfather'}
    },
    {
        id:17,
        question:'17.What power does Asta have in "Black Clover"?',
        option:{
            a:'Heat Magic',
            b:'Magic Nullifier',
            c:'Water Magic',
            d:'Strength Magic',
        },
        answer:{b:'Magic Nullifier'}
    },
    {
        id:18,
        question:"18.What is Naruto's main goal?",
        option:{
            a:'Find His Parents',
            b:'Avenge His Brother',
            c:'Save His Sister',
            d:'To Be The Leader Of His Village',
        },        
        answer:{d:'To Be The Leader Of His Village'}
    },
    {
        id:19,
        question:'19.Which anime includes the Elric brothers Edward and Alphonse?',
        option:{
            a:'Gintama',
            b:'Fullmetal Alchemist',
            c:'Koe no Katach',
            d:'The Rising Of The Shield Hero',
        },    
        answer:{b:'Fullmetal Alchemist'}    
    },
    {
        id:20,
        question:'20.The ghouls of Anteiku are known to be friendly in "Tokyo Ghoul" what is Anteiku?',
        option:{
            a:'A Restaurant',
            b:'A Town',
            c:'A Coffee Shop',
            d:'A Bar',
        },        
        answer:{c:'A Coffee Shop'}   
    },
    {
        id:21,
        question:'21.Who is the leader of the homunculi in "Fullmetal Alchemist"?',
        option:{
            a:'Dante',
            b:'Edward',
            c:'Riza',
            d:'Izumi',
        },     
        answer:{a:'Dante'}   
    },
    {
        id:22,
        question:'22.Who created the House of Evolution in "One-Punch Man"?',
        option:{
            a:'Ground Dragon',
            b:'Zombieman',
            c:'Beast King',
            d:'Dr. Genus',
        },     
        answer:{d:'Dr. Genus'}
    }
]